

# Carl Jerwin Gensaya

# Full-stack Developer



# **Summary**

I am Computer Science graduate that has experience on web development and other mainstream programming/scripting languages. The passion that I have on my earlier college life has always been on the back-end side of developing but I am planning on honing my skills on front-end development as well.



# **Personal Info**

#### Address

6003 CF Natividad St. Mapulang Lupa, Valenzuela City

#### Phone

09167724968

#### Date of birth

1995-04-19

#### www

crlwingen.github.io/crlwingen

#### GitHub

github.com/crlwingen

#### Google+

crlwingen@gmail.com



### Skills

C#

CSS/HTML

••••

Git

••••

Java

••••

Javascript

Python

## **Experience**

2017-04 -2017-05

## Full-stack Developer | Software Engineer (Intern)

Save22 Inc. Engineering Department

- Worked on the Engineering Department for external projects of the Company.
- Developed front-end and back-end for an Ionic mobile application.

2017-11 -2018-02

# Full-stack Developer | Software Engineer (Remote)

Save22 Inc.

- Developed front-end and back-end for a website. (https://www.communiteer.org/)
- Created web scrapers for multiple online shopping websites.



### Education

2014-06 -2018-05

# Polytechnic University of the Philippines

- Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Major in Computer Science Research
- Thesis: MananalaysAl: Fully-automated Filipino Story Generator using BRNN (Python)